Contact

ray.debra@hotmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/debra-burks-ray-77949055 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Healthcare
Microsoft Office
Microsoft Excel

Debra Burks Ray

Experienced Interim Nursing Leader; HealthTrust Workforce Solutions

Kansas City, Missouri Area

Summary

I am a Masters prepared expert Labor and Delivery RN with extensive clinical as well as leadership and management experience.

I am certified by NCC in Inpatient Obstetrics and by IBCLE as an International Board Certified Lactation Consultant.

I have a strong commitment to providing compassionate, high quality, evidenced based nursing care to women and infants, and educating/leading others to do the same.

Experience

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions; Good Samaritan Hospital Interim Manager, Mother/Baby Unit, Good Samaritan Hospital, San Jose, CA

January 2020 - May 2020 (5 months)

San Jose, California

Research Medical Center

Transitional Leader, Interim Manager, Women and Infant Services. July 2019 - January 2020 (7 months)

Sinai-Grace Hospital

Interim Administrative Director Women and Infant Services May 2018 - June 2019 (1 year 2 months)

Detroit, Michigan

Interim Administrative Director of Women and Infant Services.

St Joseph East, Women's Hospital Registered Nurse August 2017 - May 2018 (10 months) Lexington, KY

Medical Solutions

L&D RN

May 2017 - July 2017 (3 months)

LewisGale Medical Center MSN, BSN, RNC-OB, IBCLC; Director, Maternity Care Center October 2013 - March 2017 (3 years 6 months)

Salem, Virginia

Medical Solutions
Obstetrics RN, Travel
September 2012 - October 2013 (1 year 2 months)
L&D Nursing, Lactation Consultant

Frankfort Regional Medical Center MSN, RNC-OB, IBCLC; Director, The Center for Womens Health February 2000 - August 2012 (12 years 7 months)

Director, The Center for Women's Health Staff RN Lactation Consultant

Education

Indiana Wesleyan University
Bachelor of Science, Nursing, Master of Science, Nursing, Education
Track · (2004 - 2008)

Methodist Hospital School of Nursing Nursing Diploma, Nursing · (1979 - 1981)